<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Political Categories on Reden Communications</title><link>/categories/</link><description>Recent content in Political Categories on Reden Communications</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Members of Parliament</title><link>/category/members-of-parliament/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>/category/members-of-parliament/</guid><description>Members of Parliament (MPs) represent the interests and concerns of the public in the House of Commons. MPs consider and can propose new laws as well as raising their constituents&amp;rsquo; issues. MPs split their time between working in Parliament itself, working in the constituency that elected them and working for their political party.</description></item><item><title>Lords</title><link>/category/lords/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate><guid>/category/lords/</guid><description>The House of Lords is made up of around 800 members from a variety of professions and walks of life. The Lords shares the task of making and shaping laws and checking and challenging the work of the government.</description></item><item><title>Parliamentary Assistants</title><link>/category/parliamentary-assistants/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate><guid>/category/parliamentary-assistants/</guid><description>Parliamentary assistants carry out research and office work for Members of Parliament. They work at the House of Commons or in the MP&amp;rsquo;s constituency office. They are sometimes called politician’s assistants, political researchers or caseworkers if they work in the constituency office.</description></item><item><title>Lords Assistants</title><link>/category/lords-assistants/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate><guid>/category/lords-assistants/</guid><description>Lords assistants carry out research and office work for Members of the House of Lords.</description></item><item><title>Special Advisers</title><link>/category/special-advisers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate><guid>/category/special-advisers/</guid><description>Special advisers (SpAds) are political appointees hired to support ministers. They give party political advice and support that would be inappropriate for the civil service to provide. Special advisers often have close working relationships with their ministers and some continue advising the same minister as they move between briefs.</description></item><item><title>Government Communication Service</title><link>/category/government-communication-service/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>/category/government-communication-service/</guid><description>The Government Communication Service is the professional body for public service communicators working in government departments, agencies and arm’s length bodies. They deliver public service communications to support ministers’ priorities and enable the efficient and effective operation of public services.</description></item></channel></rss>